http://cugc.uk/privacy-notice/

HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
— Cambridge University Golf Club (“CUGC”)
This statement explains how CUGC (“we” and “our”) handles and uses data it collects about its members  for processes relating to the operation and activities of the society.
When changes are made to this statement, we will publish the updated version to our website.
The controller for your personal information is CUGC. The person responsible for data protection at the time of issue, and the person who is responsible for monitoring compliance with relevant legislation in relation to the protection of personal information, is the Junior Treasurer.
The normal legal basis for processing your personal information is that we believe it is in our legitimate interests to do so, in order for the club to run effectively and efficiently.  Where we process your personal information outside of the purposes listed in this statement, we will seek your explicit consent to do so in advance.  You may ask us for further information on these matters at any time if you have specific concerns.
THE DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW YOUR DATA IS USED BY THE CLUB
We collect and process your personal information, as specified below, for a number of purposes, including:
maintaining your personal details (i.e. your name, photograph, relevant College identifiers and preferred contact details), including ensuring effective communications with you;
maintaining financial records (i.e. payment of membership fees and other payments to the society);
maintaining a formal record of your activities within the society;
other purposes;
maintaining data to enable the club to undertake research into its own activities and/or to manage complaints made to us.
If you have concerns or queries about any of these purposes, please contact us.
HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Personal data is not shared outside of the society and its members.
We may also be subject to a legal requirement (with or without your consent) to share your personal information with a government agency (such as the police or security services or other statutory authorities with investigatory powers ) under special circumstances (e.g. relating to tax, crime or health and safety).  Where possible, we will notify you of our intention to share such information in advance.
We may share information with organisations overseas as part of arrangements related to your membership of the society.  In such cases, we will ask for your explicit consent prior to transmitting this information.
SECURITY AND CONTROLLED DATA SHARING WITH PARTNERS
All information is held and transmitted securely, and (in addition to disclosure as permitted or required by law) may be shared on a considered and confidential basis only with the University and the Colleges. The Golf Club may also facilitate communication between individual alumni, but in doing so does not release personal contact details without prior permission. Club or member information will not be shared to third parties outside of the University without explicit consent.
RETENTION
Personal information that is no longer relevant, or out of date, shall be erased. Information about how long different types of information are retained by the University is published at https://www.information- compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/records-management.
CONTROL
As a member of the club you are in control. If you have any queries, wish to be erased or restrict data processing or sharing (including use for marketing), want your information updating, or do not want certain members to be contacted by the University, please let us know. (Minimal information is always retained to make sure that members are not contacted again inadvertently).
We will publish any changes we make to this notice and notify you where appropriate.
For full details of how your personal data is used by the University while you are a student and once you are an alumnus/a, please see the statements at: https://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/student-dataand https://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/alumni-data
WHO CAN I CONTACT?
If you have any questions about how your personal information is used, or wish to exercise any of your rights, please consult the University’s data protection webpages at https://www.information- compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection. If you need further assistance, please contact the Sports Service, or, alternatively, the University’s data protection team (data.protection@admin.cam.ac.uk) or its Data Protection Officer (dpo@admin.cam.ac.uk).
YOUR RIGHTS
You have the right: to ask us for access to, rectification or erasure of your personal information; to restrict processing (pending correction or deletion); to object to communications; and to ask for the transfer of your personal information electronically to a third party (data portability).
Some of these rights are not automatic, and we reserve the right to discuss with you why we might not comply with a request from you to exercise them.
If you have questions or concerns about your personal information, or how it used, please speak an officer of the society.
If you remain unhappy with the way your information is being handled, or with the response received from us, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office at Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, SK9 5AF (https://ico.org.uk/).
LinksPrivacy Notice
Terms of Use
Social Media  : cambridgebluesgolf
: CUGC
Site by Rare Creative Group
